http://www.241pizza.com/privacy.aspx

Privacy
241 Pizza (2006) Ltd. has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for our website www.241pizza.com, all affiliated websites and contests. 241 Pizza (2006) Ltd. commits to protecting your information from unauthorized access or disclosure.
At times we will ask you to provide information that will enable us to:
complete a transaction;
provide you with important production information;
enhance your site visit;
follow-up later;
provide you with customer support services;
seek your opinion from time to time;
compile marketing and other statistics for use by us.
Your participation is optional. We will not collect any personal information about you unless you provide it to us voluntarily. For example, and not by limitation, we may collect personal information when you make a purchase, participate in a contest or promotion; fill out a questionnaire; sign up for a survey or otherwise interact with us.
We may ask for your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, information about a product your have purchased, or other information. We may also keep records of previous purchases made by you, information we have provided to you, and details of any enquiries, complaints or compliments made by you and our response, if any.
Demographic and profile data may be collected. In order to understand your preferences better. This information is used to help us provide you with better service, products and offers of interest to you from www.241pizza.com and related businesses.
When you provide personal information to us, we may ask if you wish to receive future communication from us such as newsletters, emails or other information. You may choose not to receive this communication at the time we ask it; you may opt-out by clicking on the link at the bottom of any email you received from us or, if you would like your name removed from our database, you may do so by sending an email with "unsubscribe" in the subject line to offers@241pizza.com.
We do not knowingly collect personal information for anyone under 18 years of age. If we learn you are under 18 years of age, we will not maintain or use your personal information. This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities offered by us.
We will not share your personal information with anyone outside of 241 Pizza (2006) Ltd and its affiliated companies except to the extent necessary to fulfill the purposes described. When we employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf – such as delivering products, sending postal or electronic mail, analyzing data, taking product orders, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and providing other forms of customer service – and where we collect personal information with third parties, we ensure by contractual means that these third parties may not use your personal information for any other purpose without your knowledge and consent.
We reserve the right at any time to collect, use or disclose any information:
To satisfy any law, regulation or government request;
If such disclosure is necessary or appropriate for site or system operation;
To protect the rights, property or safety of 241 Pizza (2006) Ltd, its customers, site visitors, or others.
By providing us with your personal information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement. These terms and conditions are subject to change, so you may wish to review them periodically.
ONLINE ORDERING SIGN IN
First Visit
Enter your phone number to create an account and order online.
It's quick and easy.
POSTAL CODE:
PHONE NUMBER:
NEW ACCOUNT
Returning
For returning customers who already have an account.
EMAIL ADDRESS:
PASSWORD:
SIGN IN
Help, I forgot my password.
Guest
Just curious?
Feel free to surf our menu and see what's cooking at your local 241 Pizza.
POSTAL CODE:
GUEST ACCESS
We respect your privacy and we don't share or sell your personal information.
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
WELCOME
Enter your phone number to create an account and order online. It’s quick and easy.
POSTAL CODE
PHONE NUMBER
NEW ACCOUNT
We respect your privacy and we don’t share or sell your
personal information.
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
WELCOME BACK
Please log in to order.
EMAIL
PASSWORD
LOGIN
Opps, I
forgot my password.
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
GUEST
Just curious?
Feel free to surf our menu and see what's cooking at your local 241 Pizza.
POSTAL CODE
GUEST ACCESS
We respect your privacy and we don’t share or sell your
personal information.
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
CREATE YOUR ACCOUNT NOW
Complete this short form to create your account.
Remember your password for quick ordering on your next visit.
ADDRESS LABEL (e.g.,home,grandma's)
We respect your Privacy and we don't share or sell your personal information.
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
WELCOME
Please enter your street number in the field below.
YOUR STREET NUMBER:
SUBMIT
We respect your privacy and we don’t share or sell your
personal information.
Need Help?
We respect your privacy and we don't share or sell your personal information.
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
READY TO ORDER
You are successfully logged in.
TO
NOW OR LATER:
-- Please choose --
RIGHT NOW
LATER
DATE:
TIME:
SEARCH (postal code or street and city)
SEARCH
DEFAULT (My Last Pickup location)
SELECT
or
SEARCH (postal code or street and city)
SEARCH
Show More
READY TO PLACE ORDER
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
SELECT DELIVERY ADDRESS
READY TO PLACE ORDER
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
SELECT YOUR DELIVERY LOCATION
You can only select locations that are open at the time you have selected.
Product availability and pricing may change from area to area, changing your delivery location later may require your cart to be cleared.
ADD A NEW DELIVERY ADDRESS
GO BACK
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
Add a new delivery address
ADDRESS LABEL (e.g. , home, grandma's)
POSTAL CODE
GO BACK
We don't share any of your personal information, click here for our Privacy Policy
Need Help?
We don't share any of your personal information, click here for our Privacy Policy
Need Help?
Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
New Address saved
Continue with your order
Your new Delivery Address has been saved and stored in your Account page.
NOW OR LATER:
-- Please choose --
RIGHT NOW
LATER
DATE:
TIME:
DELIVER TO:
GO BACK
CONTINUE
Need Help? Call us at 416-241-0-241or 1-866-241-0-241
